Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Year group portrait. 17.1 x 22.9 cm, 1946/47; 10123; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref745)
  Arabic Writing; Teachers; Children; Men; Students; Boys; Priests/Clergymen; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt
- Class photo. 17.7 x 23.3 cm, 1957/58; 10125; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref746)
  Boys; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Uniforms; Women; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Priests/Clergymen
- Class photo. 16.9 x 23 cm, 1957/58; 10126; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref747)
  Boys; Priests/Clergymen; Students; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Men; Group Portraits; Teachers; Schools/Education
- Class photo. 17.5 x 23.3 cm, 1957/58; 10127; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref748)
  Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Men; Schools/Education; Boys; Children; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Uniforms; Facial Hair
- School band.11.7 x 18.1 cm, Circa 1910; 10128; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref749)
  Uniforms; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Students; Men; Schools/Education; Musical Instruments; Painted Backdrops; Teachers; Boys; Woodwind Instruments; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Musicians; Photographic Prints; Brass Instruments; Children; Facial Hair
- A woman standing with four boys at a school event. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10129; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref750)
  Women; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Medals/Insignia; Color Photography; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Schools/Education
- School awards ceremony. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10130; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref751)
  Teachers; Awards; Men; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Students; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- A teacher being awarded with a trophy. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10131; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref752)
  Awards; Women; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Men; Color Photography; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- A teacher shaking hands with a priest at a school awards ceremony. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10132; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref753)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Awards; Men; Schools/Education; Head Covers/Veils; Teachers; Color Photography; Women; Facial Hair
- A school awards ceremony. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10133; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref754)
  Color Photography; Awards; Teachers; Schools/Education; Men; Students; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Flags; Children; Priests/Clergymen
- Teachers with a student during a school awards ceremony. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10134; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref755)
  Boys; Color Photography; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Men
- A school awards ceremony. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10135; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref756)
  Color Photography; Awards; Men; Turbans; Teachers; Children; Students; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- A school awards ceremony. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10136; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref757)
  Students; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Flags; Awards; Teachers
- School choir and band at a school event. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10137; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref758)
  Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Photographic Prints; Girls; Musical Instruments; Schools/Education; Teachers; Students; Choirs; Children; Uniforms; Men; Singing
- A man giving a speech at a school event. 12.4 x 8.8 cm, 1983-1984; 10138; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref759)
  Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Cameras; Microphones; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Speeches
- Musical performance at a school event. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10139; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref760)
  Children; Musical Instruments; Singing; Teachers; Girls; Men; Photographic Prints; Boys; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Students; Choirs; Schools/Education; Flags
- Parents in the audience at a school event. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 1983-1984; 10140; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref761)
  Audiences/Spectators; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Girls; Children; Boys; Students; Carpets/Rugs; Events/Occasions; Group Portraits; Cameras; Facial Hair
- Group photo of students wearing scout uniforms. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10141; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref762)
  Children; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Scouts; Boys; Color Photography; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- A teacher receiving a trophy at a school award ceremony. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10142; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref763)
  Awards; Schools/Education; Women; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Men; Facial Hair
- Parents and students in the audience at a school event. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10143; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref764)
  Children; Schools/Education; Women; Audiences/Spectators; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Color Photography; Boys; Medals/Insignia; Girls; Balloons; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Musical performance at a school event. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10144; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref765)
  Color Photography; Children; Musicians; Musical Instruments; Singing; Choirs; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Boys; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Students
- A student receiving a medal at a school award ceremony. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10145; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref766)
  Students; Teachers; Uniforms; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Color Photography; Regional/National Dress; Photographic Prints; Medals/Insignia; Schools/Education; Children; Awards; Ceremonies
- Group portrait during a school award ceremony. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10146; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref767)
  Color Photography; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Awards; Schools/Education; Students; Children; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Group portrait. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10147; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref768)
  Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Men; Women; Awards; Group Portraits; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- A group portrait at a school event. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10148; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref769)
  Awards; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Men; Women; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Teachers at school event. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10150; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref770)
  Color Photography; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Women; Teachers; Men; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Group portrait of students. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10151; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref771)
  Schools/Education; Bow Ties; Children; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Students; Boys; Uniforms
- Students holding flags during school event. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10152; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref772)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Students; Flags; Parades/Processions; Boys; Children
- Group portrait of teachers. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10153; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref773)
  Teachers; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Women; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Group photo of school staff. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10154; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref774)
  Arabic Writing; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Tea/Coffee; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Women; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of school staff. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10155; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref775)
  Women; Color Photography; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Group photo of teachers. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10156; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref776)
  Color Photography; Schools/Education; Jewelry; Teachers; Group Portraits; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Group photo of school staff, including a scout leader. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, Undated; 10157; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref777)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Men; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Medals/Insignia; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Scouts; Women; Facial Hair
- A teacher speaking into a microphone during a school event. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, 1983-1984; 10158; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref778)
  Microphones; Teachers; Schools/Education; Speeches; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Students in line during an honoring ceremony. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10159; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref779)
  Awards; Students; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Teachers; Schools/Education; Men
- Student receiving an award during an honoring ceremony in school. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10160; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref780)
  Schools/Education; Teachers; Awards; Students; Men; Photographic Prints; Boys; Cameras; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography
- Students playing drums during a school event.12.4 x 8.8 cm, 1983-1984; 10161; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref781)
  Women; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Children; Musical Instruments; Boys; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Head Covers/Veils; Medals/Insignia
- Group photo of police officers with school staff. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10162; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref782)
  Color Photography; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Children; Police; Students; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Group photo of two women with children. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10163; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref783)
  Color Photography; Girls; Schools/Education; Children; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Two teachers with a student. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10164; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref784)
  Men; Children; Food; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Students; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Boys; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- Group photo of men at the school. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10165; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref785)
  Color Photography; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- Group photo of school staff. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10166; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref786)
  Teachers; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- Girls singing during a school event. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10167; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref787)
  Children; Uniforms; Choirs; Color Photography; Students; Singing; Girls; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- School staff. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10168; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref788)
  Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Facial Hair
- Boys singing during a school event. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1983-1984; 10169; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref789)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Students; Choirs; Singing; Children; Uniforms; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Boys
- Students carrying school flags in a school event. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 10170; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref790)
  Uniforms; Parades/Processions; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Schools/Education; Flags; Students; Marching Band; Boys; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Boy scouts holding flags. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 10171; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref791)
  Marching Band; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Scouts; Children; Flags; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Boys; Helwan, Egypt
- Students marching and carrying flags in the city. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 10172; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref792)
  Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Outdoors; Students; Photographic Prints; Men; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Buildings; Architecture; Flags; Streets/Roads; Children; Color Photography; Parades/Processions; Police
- Boy scouts marching with flags. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 10173; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref793)
  Outdoors; Flags; Streets/Roads; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Scouts; Parades/Processions; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Buildings; Architecture
- School's taekwondo team marching in the street.10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 10174; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref794)
  Sports; Students; Boys; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Men; Architecture; Schools/Education; Teachers; Outdoors; Cars/Trucks; Color Photography; Police; Photographic Prints; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Parades/Processions; Transportation
- Marching band. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 10175; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref795)
  Men; Parades/Processions; Brass Instruments; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Flags; Outdoors; Buildings; Uniforms; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Musical Instruments; Helwan, Egypt; Marching Band; Facial Hair
- Girls marching with trophies. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 10176; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref796)
  Color Photography; Children; Parades/Processions; Men; Outdoors; Flags; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Uniforms; Students; Photographic Prints; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Awards
- Boys marching with flags and trophies. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 10177; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref797)
  Flags; Buses; Students; Streets/Roads; Outdoors; Boys; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Parades/Processions; Street Lamps; Children; Transportation; Awards; Group Portraits
- Students marching in the street. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988; 10178; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref798)
  Outdoors; Architecture; Children; Buildings; Boys; Parades/Processions; Girls; Color Photography; Students; Streets/Roads; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
- Boys marching in the street. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988; 10179; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref799)
  Uniforms; Color Photography; Parades/Processions; Streets/Roads; Students; Outdoors; Architecture; Buildings; Men; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt
- Boys marching in the street. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 10180; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref800)
  Arabic Writing; Uniforms; Outdoors; Buildings; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Men; Boys; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Parades/Processions; Color Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Teachers; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Students marching in the street. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10181; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref801)
  Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Girls; Students; Men; Boys; Outdoors; Streets/Roads; Awards; Uniforms; Flags; Schools/Education; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Parades/Processions; Kiosks/Kushk; Street Lamps
- Boys marching in the street. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10182; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref802)
  Boys; Men; Students; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Parades/Processions; Outdoors; Streets/Roads; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers
- Students marching in the streets celebrating the 100th anniversary of Holy Family School. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10183; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref803)
  Transportation; Parades/Processions; Color Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Buses; Boys; Girls; Cars/Trucks; Schools/Education; Men; Cameras; Buildings; Women; Streets/Roads; Students; Uniforms; Religious Sites; Children
- Man speaking in front of students. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated; 10184; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref804)
  Uniforms; Uniforms; Men; Scouts; Children; Parades/Processions; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Outdoors; Boys; Flags; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait of the taekwondo team. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10185; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref805)
  Schools/Education; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Students; Boys; Sports; Uniforms; Children; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of students wearing sashes. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10186; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref806)
  Students; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Boys; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Children; Outdoors; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt
- Taekwondo team performing in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10187; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref807)
  Children; Uniforms; Boys; Outdoors; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Crowds; Sports; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Students; Men; Group Portraits
- Group portrait of men and nuns.10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10188; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref808)
  Photographic Prints; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Nuns; Group Portraits; Men; Schools/Education; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Group of men smiling. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10189; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref809)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Facial Hair
- Boy scouts performing in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10190; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref810)
  Scouts; Uniforms; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Crowds; Tents; Audiences/Spectators; Boys; Students
- A man speaking into a microphone standing next to a table of trophies. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10191; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref811)
  Schools/Education; Women; Awards; Men; Scouts; Speeches; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Helwan, Egypt; Microphones; Musical Instruments
- Boy scouts demonstrating their skills in front of crowd. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10192; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref812)
  Scouts; Boys; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Uniforms; Color Photography; Students; Nuns; Children; Audiences/Spectators
- Girls choir singing on stage. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10193; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref813)
  Nuns; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Musical Instruments; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Students; Singing; Children; Girls; Uniforms
- A group portrait of students wearing sashes. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; 10194; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref814)
  Schools/Education; Color Photography; Students; Boys; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Man speaking in microphone. 10.1 x 15.1 cm, Undated; 10195; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref815)
  Speeches; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Awards; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Men; Microphones; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- The audience at a school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; 10196; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref816)
  Teachers; Color Photography; Students; Priests/Clergymen; Crowds; Schools/Education; Audiences/Spectators; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Women; Boys; Girls; Children
- The audience at a school awards ceremony. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; 10198; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref817)
  Children; Architecture; Buildings; Audiences/Spectators; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Awards; Boys; Girls; Students; Teachers; Men
- A camera man in front of the audience at a school event. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; 10199; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref818)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Cameras; Men; Women; Students; Audiences/Spectators; Teachers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Crowd at school event from above. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, Undated; 10200; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref819)
  Students; Outdoors; Audiences/Spectators; Cameras; Teachers; Women; Men; Girls; Boys; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Children